{
    "id": "8a8945202efa4fe0ada6087962d28e14",
    "title": "Two-word verbs quiz",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "554a15877b8841558def39fa0f665479",
            "title": "Two Word Verbs",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "We can’t hold ............................ the meeting any further.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "out",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The three gunmen who held ................................... the Union Bank yesterday have been caught.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "up",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Words for repeated ideas can be left ..................................... in the second of two coordinate clauses.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "off",
                        "up",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The judge looked ....................................... the papers before announcing the verdict.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "in",
                        "over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Whenever I come ............................................. an unfamiliar word, I look it up.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "upon",
                        "across",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She knew she was in trouble, so she made ....................................... a story about getting stuck in the traffic.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "up",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Although I couldn’t make ...................................... what he was saying, I kept nodding.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "off",
                        "out",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Pick ...................................... the correct answer from the given options.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "off",
                        "down"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "As we drove through the city, our guide pointed ............................. the major tourist attractions.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "off",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t want to spend this money. I will put it ...................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "away",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}